bechristianlouboutin.com 2011-05-14

# Privacy at bechristianlouboutin.com

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. www.bechristianlouboutin.com strongly promises to respect your privacy and take your online safety. You accepted this policy and consented to such collection, storage and use when you signed up for our Service.

**1.What Information to collect.**  
In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. we can use your personal information to:  
* Help make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.  
* Help you quickly find information, products, and services.  
* Help us create content on this Site that is most relevant to you.  
* Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.  
These Information includes: Registration and Ordering, Email Addresses, Cookies and Other Technology, Log Files, Product Reviews and other personal information.

**2\. How to use and disclosure information.**  
a)Collection   
You can browse our sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us.   
We may collect and store the following personal information:   
email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;  
transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as bidding, buying, selling, item and content you generate or that relates to your account);   
shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item;   
community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our sites, and correspondence sent to us;  
other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information;   
additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity or ownership of an item you list);  
information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data; and other supplemental information from third parties (for example, if you incur a debt to our site, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law)

b) Use   
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:   
provide the services and customer support you request;   
resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;   
prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;   
customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;   
tell you about our services and those of our corporate family, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; 

c) Our Disclosure of Your Information  
We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.  
We may also share your personal information with:   
Service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards).   
Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).   
Law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity. In such events, we will disclose information relevant to the investigation, such as name, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, User ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history.

d) No Spam, Spyware or Spoofing  
We and our users do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your communication preferences, so we communicate to you as you prefer. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We automatically scan and may manually filter messages to check for spam, viruses, phishing attacks and other malicious activity or illegal or prohibited content, but we do not permanently store messages sent through these tools. If you send an email to an email address that is not registered in our community (via Refer-a-Friend or other tools), we do not permanently store that email or use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses. 

**3\. How to protect Information.**  
a) Account Protection   
Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

b) Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information   
You can see, review and change most of your personal information by signing on to our site. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate.

c) Security   
We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

d) Third Parties  
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on our sites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. www.bechristianlouboutin.com does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. 

**4\. Conclusion**  
Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.
